leer.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for LEER.com

## General Statement:

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. This privacy statement explains our policies and practices regarding on-line customer information. It is through this disclosure that we intend to provide you with a level of comfort and confidence in how we collect, use, and safeguard personal and other information we collect or that you provide through this Web site, and how you can contact us if you have any questions or concerns. It is our sincere hope that by explaining our data handling practices we will develop a trusting and long-lasting relationship with you. The business purpose of this Web site is essentially twofold: (1) to provide customers with knowledge of the features and benefits of the complete LEER product line; and (2) to provide customers with purchasing-related information such as available incentives, services, product fits and dealership contacts.

## Information Regarding Truck Accessories Group, LLC Privacy Practices:

This document describes how this Web site collects and uses data about you. This includes data you provide us, as well as data we may collect about your site usage patterns. This statement pertains specifically to the leer.com Web site. If you navigate to other Web sites during your time online, it is recommended that you check the specific privacy statements of those sites before providing any personally identifiable information.

## Normal Web Site Usage:

The information we collect and store during usage of this Web site is the name of your Internet Service Provider, the Web site that referred you to us, the pages you request, and the date and time of those requests. We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of customer visits. During normal Web site usage, we do not collect or store personally identifiable information such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number or social security number.

## Collection of Personally Identifiable Information:

There are instances on the leer.com site where you may need to provide personally identifiable information in order to receive a specific product or service, such as a brochure, dealer information or contest entry. This information, such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, Vehicle Identification Number (VIN), type of request and possibly additional information, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data by LEER or its partners or affiliates and is used to fulfill your request. If you tell us at the time that you provide information and that the information should not be used as a basis for further contact, we will respect your request. The information you provide is used by LEER to improve the services we provide you. This data may be provided to our partners and affiliates for their use. This information may also be provided to our agencies for use on behalf of LEER in accordance with our proscribed privacy policy. In addition, information you provide may be shared with an authorized LEER Dealer, so we may better serve your needs. Aside from the above, it is never provided or sold to any other company for that company's independent use.

## Electronic Mail Sent to us that Contains Personal Information:

Internet users may decide to send LEER personally identifying information, for example, in a message containing information about your LEER product. We will use this information for the purpose identified in the e-mail and to enhance our understanding of you, in order to improve our service to you.

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. A revised Privacy Policy will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Any revisions will be posted at least 10 days prior to its effective date. Limited License: This Site is provided by TAG and may be used for informational purposes only. By using this Site or downloading materials from this Site, you agree to abide by the terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by these terms and conditions, do not use this Site or download materials from this Site.

Subject to your continued compliance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement, TAG grants you, a non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited right to access, use, display and listen to this Site and the information, images, sounds and text ("Materials") thereon. You agree not to interrupt or attempt to interrupt the operation of the Site in any way.

TAG authorizes you to view and download the Materials at this Site only for your personal, non-commercial use. This authorization is not a transfer of title in the Materials and copies of the Materials and is subject to the following restrictions: 1) you must retain, on all copies of the Materials downloaded, all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the Materials; 2) you may not modify the Materials in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose; and 3) you must not transfer the Materials to any other person unless you give them notice of, and they agree to accept, the obligations arising under these terms and conditions of use. This Site, including all Materials, is protected by worldwide copyright laws and treaty provisions, whether or not a copyright notice is present on the Materials. You agree to comply with all copyright laws worldwide in your use of this Site and to prevent any unauthorized copying of the Materials. Except as expressly provided herein, Truck Accessories Group, LLC does not grant any express or implied right to you under any patents, trademarks, or copyrights.

## Personally Identifiable Information We Collect From You:

When you visit leer.com we will not collect any personal information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. Personal data includes information that is particular to you such as name, street address, telephone number, and e-mail address. If you opt not to provide us with personal information you can still access our Web site, however you may be unable to participate in certain promotions or receive product information

Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you when you visit leer.com is to provide you the functionality and services that you need to have a meaningful and customized experience while using the site features. We need to collect personal information in order to fulfill a site user request such as mailing a brochure, lead generation, sending marketing or promotional materials including e-mails or other information.

## How We Use the Personally Identifiable Information We Collect:

Personally identifiable information collected on leer.com may be used to:

  * Fulfill a site user request (brochure fulfillment, lead generation, send marketing or promotional materials including e-mails or other information)
  * Respond to your comments or requests for information
  * Meet a request for or to develop new products or services
  * Make the user experience more customer-friendly
  * Generate site analytics that improve our site layout, content, product offerings and services
  * Compile user data that is stored in our corporate database and may be used for marketing and other purposes
  * Match personal data collected here with data about you that we collect offline
  * Comply with legal requirements

## Other (Non-Personally Identifiable) Information We Collect From Site Visitors:

During a normal visit to our site, no personally identifiable information about you is collected. All information on our site is free to browse at your leisure without the need for you to provide us with any personally identifiable information. Leer.com collects other information, non-personally identifiable information from site visitors. This means that we do not track these items on an individual basis that identifies the site visitor, but rather gather and collect this information on an aggregate [or anonymous] basis that includes all site visitors. Non-personal information includes tracking the site pages that are visited, the amount of time spent on our site, clicks, page views, events (which shopping tools you interacted with), and zip code.

Our primary goal in collecting aggregate information from you is to be able to perform site metrics that allow us to improve the functionality of the Web site. We need to collect aggregate information in order to track page visits, site click through analysis, peak site usage times and site layout re-design.

We may use session and persistent "cookies," session logs, or links to collect aggregate or other non-personally identifiable information about site visitors. An explanation for each of these items and how they work is included in Section 7 Methods We Use to Collect Information.

## How We Use the Aggregate or Non-Personally Identifiable Information We Collect:

Non-Personally identifiable information collected on leer.com may be used to:

  * Compile aggregate and statistical data to help in Web site design and to identify popular features
  * Measure site activity to allow us to update our site to better meet user wants and needs

Leer.com utilizes session log data and your personal and non-personal data for the purpose of performing analytics on the users' experience while visiting this site. This analysis:

  * Is performed on an aggregate level and does not identify you or your information personally
  * Involves the use of a third party vendor acting on behalf of leer.com 
  * Is performed in order to improve our Web site and the user experience

Any information that is provided to the third party vendor is to be used only for the purpose of performing the analytics and compiling reports of the data. The third party vendor is restricted from using this data in any other way other than to provide these services to Truck Accessories Group, LLC and they may not share or resell this data

## Methods We Use to Collect Information:

A "cookie" is a small text file that helps us in many ways to make your visit to our Web site more enjoyable and meaningful to you. For example, cookies avoid you having to log in every time you come back to one of our Web sites. They also allow us to tailor a Web site or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. There are a couple different types of cookies.

A "session" cookie is stored only in your computer's working memory (RAM) and only lasts for your browsing session. When you close all your browser's windows, or when you shut down your computer, the session cookie disappears forever.

A "persistent" cookie is stored on your computer's hard drive until a specified date, which could be tomorrow, next week, or 10 years from now. Persistent cookies stay on your computer until either a) they expire, b) they are overwritten with newer cookies, c) you manually remove them. Most browsers can be configured not to accept cookies, however, this may prevent you from having access to some site functions or features.

Leer.com may use spot light ads/web beacons/GIF/pixel tags which are site instrumentation tools that help us to determine, for instance, whether a page has been viewed or not and, if so, how many times. When you ask us to send you information on a promotion or a newsletter, we may use web beacons to establish how many of the emails are actually opened. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon.

When you visit our Web site the server housing the pages automatically generates a "session log." We use session logs to help us determine how people travel through our site. In this way, we can structure our pages so that the information most frequently visited is easier to find. By tracking page visits, we can also determine if the information we're providing is being used. The only data gathered is the Internet Protocol (IP) address from which you came (which contains no personal information), the web site that referred you, the pages you visited and the date and time of those visits.

Users may be directed to leer.com via banner ads or site links. Ads or site links that are placed by leer.com use cookies or web beacons to deliver metrics on the effectiveness of the ads or links. They do not collect personal information from the user.

## Sharing Your Information:

Personal information that you provide to us in the course of requesting a product or service through this Web site may be gathered and stored in one or more of our corporate databases and be used for purposes of contacting you for things like promotional offers, marketing programs, or other communications from this Web site or from other TAG-owned Web sites.

We may share personal information that we collect about you with other companies within the TAG family of companies or subsidiaries. Our "family of companies" is the group of companies related to us by common control or ownership. We share information within this "family" as a normal part of conducting business and offering products and services to our customers.

Personal information that you provide to leer.com may be shared with our Authorized LEER Dealers. This is necessary in order to honor your request for a price quote on a vehicle or in order to provide a dealer with information for purposes of contacting you in their regular course of business. The dealer is not restricted by leer.com in their use of your data.

Vendors, contractors or partners of leer.com who have access to your personal information in connection with providing services for leer.com are required to keep the information confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for leer.com.

Leer.com may share your information with subcontractors. Subcontractors are restricted from using this data in any other way other than to provide these services to Truck Accessories Group, LLC and they may not share or resell this data.

Site metrics for leer.com may be shared with other Truck Accessories Group, LLC Web sites or subsidiaries or affiliates. The information shared will be aggregate data and will not include any of your personally identifiable information.

Leer.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Truck Accessories Group, LLC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Truck Accessories Group, LLC and this site; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Truck Accessories Group, LLC, its web sites, or the public.

## Security of Your Information:

Safeguarding information of visitors to our Web site is important to us. We use systems, policies and procedures to maintain accuracy of information and to protect information from loss, misuse or alteration.

When you send personal information, such as name, address and telephone numbers, to leer.com we use "Secure Socket Layers" or SSL to protect your data. SSL is encryption technology that helps safeguard your personal information against misuse by unauthorized individuals.

Vendors, contractors or partners of leer.com who have access to your personal information in connection with providing services for leer.com are required to keep the information confidential.

Vendors are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for leer.com.

## Links to Other Sites:

Leer.com provides links to other Web sites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of all sites which you visit, including those whose links are provided so that you can understand how those sites collect, use and share your information. Leer.com is not responsible for the privacy statements, content or data handling practices on other Web sites.

## Children's Privacy

Leer.com does not knowingly intend to collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If a child has provided us with personal information, a parent or guardian of that child may contact us at:

UNITED STATES  
Telephone  
574-522-5337

Available 8:00 am - 5:00 pm local time  
Monday - Friday

Mailing Address: Truck Accessories Group, LLC  
Marketing  
28858 Ventura Drive  
Elkhart, IN 46517

if they want this information deleted from our records. We will then make reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from the database that stores information for leer.com.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this online privacy statement for leer.com, leern.com privacy practices, or have any questions regarding the contents of this Web site please contact us at:

UNITED STATES Telephone 574-522-5337

Available 8:00 am - 5:00 pm local time Monday - Friday

Mailing Address Truck Accessories Group, LLC Marketing 28858 Ventura Drive Elkhart, IN 46517

Leer.com is committed to working with consumers to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any complaints or disputes about privacy and the handling of your data. Leer.com will be happy to respond to your questions and comments.

## Trademark Notice:

All trademarks displayed on this site are subject to the U.S. trademark rights of Truck Accessories Group, LLC (TAG) or are used under agreement in the U.S. by TAG. These trademarks include, but are not limited to, product brand names (e.g., LEER, Pace Edwards, Thule, etc.), cap and tonneau model names (e.g., 100XQ, 100XL, 100XR, 100R, 100RCC, 180, 180CC, 122, 800, 700, 550, DCC, etc.), slogans (e.g., Live, Work, Play, etc.), and logos and emblems. The unauthorized use of any trademark displayed on this site is strictly prohibited.

## Copyright Notice:

Copyright ©2010, Truck Accessories Group, LLC (TAG). All rights reserved. All text, images, graphics, animation, videos, music, sounds and other materials on this Web site ("Site") are subject to the copyrights and other intellectual property rights of TAG, its affiliated companies and its licensors. TAG owns the copyrights in the selection, coordination and arrangement of the materials on this Site. These materials may not be copied for commercial use or distribution, nor may these materials be modified or reposted to other sites.

Privacy Statement Effective Date and Revision Days Occasionally we may update the privacy statement for leer.com in order to reflect any changes to the Web site or our privacy practices. If we update this statement, the new statement will be posted to the Web site ten (10) days prior to the changes taking effect.

The effective date of this privacy statement is 7/8/2010
